<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Leia</title>
 <link href="http://leiac.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://leiac.me/"/>
 <updated>2017-06-08T15:57:06-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://leiac.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Leia Chang</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>DevMoment No. 1 - Where's OpenGL?</title>
   <link href="http://leiac.me/2017/01/24/OpenGL-Headache-1.html"/>
   <updated>2017-01-24T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://leiac.me/2017/01/24/OpenGL-Headache-#1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In a moment of command-blindness today, I managed to delete my entire repo of developing projects. No harm, of course - they were all git repos, and backed up on the internet. Simple matter of going to BitBucket and re-cloning, right? So first things first - grab my last project, re-clone it, get back to working in no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except when I tried to re-compile, it failed. At 5%. Looking like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://leiac.me/assets/OpenGL_header_missing.png&quot; alt=&quot;are you kidding me&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How the hell was I not finding ‘OpenGL/gl.h’?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still don’t know quite what I did, but it only took 20 minutes for me to go from rendering collision-detecting dogs to not being able to compile squat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two hours, a half dozen fix attempts, and many StackOverflow tabs later, I get to this: &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/18647976/missing-opengl-headers-on-mac&quot;&gt;Missing OpenGL Headers on Mac&lt;/a&gt;, which linked to yet another StackOverflow question … It turns out that even if you have Xcode installed, Command Line Tools doesn’t come with it anymore. Which means the headers I was looking for didn’t even exist at this point.
Bully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least the fix was easy. TLDR:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;xcode-select --install
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running the above launches a dialogue that allows you to install CLT. And now we’re all back up and running!
How did I somehow remove my Command Line Tools and OpenGL headers? Still no idea. A few misfired commands can go a long way. Thanks, version control!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Stop Being the Intern</title>
   <link href="http://leiac.me/2017/01/10/medium.html"/>
   <updated>2017-01-10T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://leiac.me/2017/01/10/medium</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;New post on Medium: &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@leilisms/stop-being-the-intern-31d49c74f167#.t0cb4bxk0&quot;&gt;Stop Being The Intern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>And So It Begins</title>
   <link href="http://leiac.me/2016/08/03/it-begins.html"/>
   <updated>2016-08-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://leiac.me/2016/08/03/it-begins</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;That’s right, I made about the simplest personal website in existence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? Well, first of all there’s a lot to be said about the use of personal websites for self promotion. It feels like in order to be competitive, you’ve got to have a suave, minimalist business card, a beefed-up portolio, and a pretty website to go along with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in the end, this is a place for me to play around with some web design, see how far I can push GitHub Pages and Jekyll in my experiments. This page might change a lot, and it’s all in good fun. Let’s see if I can hook up a sweet Flickr slideshow embed, or figure out how the heck paginator works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For anyone else interested in playing around with this, here’s some stuff to start out with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home/&quot;&gt;JekyllRB Docs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.github.com/categories/github-pages-basics/&quot;&gt;Github Pages Basics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
